(soft music)
♪ Nobody on the road ♪
♪ Nobody on the beach ♪
♪ I feel it in the air ♪
♪ The summer's out of reach ♪
♪ Empty lake, empty streets ♪
♪ The sun goes down alone ♪
♪ I'm driving by your house ♪
♪ Though I know
you're not home ♪
♪ But I can see you ♪
♪ Your brown skin
shining in the sun ♪
♪ You got your hair
combed back and your ♪
♪ Sunglasses on, baby ♪
♪ I can tell you, my love for
you will still be strong ♪
♪ After the boys of
summer have gone ♪
(soft music)
♪ I never will
forget those nights ♪
♪ I wonder if it was a dream ♪
♪ Remember how
you made me crazy ♪
I made you scream ♪
♪ Now I don't understand
what happened to our love ♪
♪ But babe,
I'm gonna get you back ♪
♪ I'm going to show
you what I'm made of ♪
♪ I can see you ♪
♪ Your brown skin
shining in the sun ♪
♪ I see you
walking real slow and ♪
♪ Smiling at everyone ♪
♪ I can tell you, my love for
you will still be strong ♪
♪ After the boys of
summer have gone ♪
(soft music)
♪ Out on the road today ♪
♪ I saw a Deadhead
sticker on a Cadillac ♪
♪ A little voice
inside my head said ♪
♪ Don't look back,
you can never look back ♪
♪ I thought I knew what
love was, what did I know ♪
♪ Those days are gone forever ♪
♪ I should just
let them go but ♪
♪ I can see you ♪
♪ Your brown skin
shining in the sun ♪
♪ You got the top
pulled down and the ♪
♪ Radio on, baby ♪
♪ I can tell you, my love for
you will still be strong ♪
♪ After the boys of
summer have gone ♪
♪ I can see you ♪
♪ Your brown skin
shining in the sun ♪
♪ You got your hair
slicked back and those ♪
♪ Wayfarers on, baby ♪
♪ I can tell you, my love for
you will still be strong ♪
♪ After the boys of
summer have gone ♪
(soft music)